const myCardsTitle = [
  {
    levelNumber: "2.8",
    title: "Wh questions + Present Continuous",
  },
];

const myCards = [
  {
    front: "Gdzie idziesz?",
    back: "Where are you going?",
  },
  {
    front: "Kiedy zaczynasz kurs?",
    back: "When are you starting the course?",
  },
  {
    front: "Dlaczego płaczesz?",
    back: "Why are you crying?",
  },
  {
    front: "Jak się masz?",
    back: "How are you doing?",
  },
  {
    front: "Gdzie on jedzie na urlop?",
    back: "Where is he going on holiday?",
  },
  {
    front: "Do kogo on mówi?",
    back: "Who is he talking to?",
  },
  {
    front: "Dlaczego on zmienia pracę?",
    back: "Why is he changing his job?",
  },
  {
    front: "Kiedy wyjeżdża?",
    back: "When is he leaving?",
  },
  {
    front: "Gdzie ona siedzi?",
    back: "Where is she sitting?",
  },
  {
    front: "Co ona czyta?",
    back: "What is she reading?",
  },
  {
    front: "Kiedy ona wraca?",
    back: "When is she coming back?",
  },
  {
    front: "Jak ona sobie radzi?",
    back: "How is she doing?",
  },
  {
    front: "Co tak hałasuje?",
    back: "What is making that noise?",
  },
  {
    front: "Dlaczego to się nie rusza?",
    back: "Why is it not moving?",
  },
  {
    front: "Kiedy przyjdzie paczka?",
    back: "When is the parcel coming?",
  },
  {
    front: "Dlaczego tak szybko się to zmienia?",
    back: "Why is it changing so fast?",
  },
  {
    front: "Dlaczego wciąż czekamy?",
    back: "Why are we still waiting?",
  },
  {
    front: "Gdzie idziemy?",
    back: "Where are we going?",
  },
  {
    front: "Kiedy wracamy?",
    back: "When are we coming back?",
  },
  {
    front: "Gdzie lecisz?",
    back: "Where are you flying?",
  },
  {
    front: "Kiedy przeprowadzasz się do nowego domu?",
    back: "When are you moving to the new house?",
  },
  {
    front: "Jak się czujesz?",
    back: "How are you feeling?",
  },
  {
    front: "Co planujesz?",
    back: "What are you planning?",
  },
  {
    front: "Gdzie się spotykają?",
    back: "Where are they meeting?",
  },
  {
    front: "Co oni gotują?",
    back: "What are they cooking?",
  },
  {
    front: "Dlaczego oni krzyczą?",
    back: "Why are they shouting?",
  },
  {
    front: "Z kim rozmawiam?",
    back: "Who am I speaking with?",
  },
  {
    front: "Jak się mam?",
    back: "How am I doing?",
  },
  {
    front: "Gdzie idę po pracy?",
    back: "Where am I going after work?",
  },
  {
    front: "Co oglądam?",
    back: "What am I watching?",
  },
];

export { myCardsTitle, myCards };
